Hello, these are the recordings
of John Greenwitch
I'm working for the Project Pandora as a
Biologist for the Prometheus Corporation
Ehm... and I... still can't
believe to be here
Huh! I mean, it' s not about
the salary, it's about...
working on a real
Priority Two project
The equipment is unbelievable,
the possibilities, the the...
THIS is science at the highest level
God, am I happy to be here
Huh!
Day 21
This virus is still a
puzzle to all of us
It's mutating so fast and
it is so contagious,
how can we ever manage
to develop an antidote?
Not speaking of synthesizing
it for everybody
Of course, the executive board was
not particularly happy about it, but
despite falling revenues, we have
been upgraded to Priority One
Which means, we get more
money for this project
I hope, this will help us a bit
Day 47
We got a step closer
to the antidote
but it is still a long way to go
It seems that the virus is mutating,
changing its DNA structure again and again
And the antidote?
The antidote has to match this
DNA structure precisely
That means, we will never manage
to produce an antidote
long time in advance
We have a long way to go
Day 84
We have taken a great step forward
Anderson perfected the antidote
I believe, with the right DNA coding,
we can stop the virus
The management was impressed
but not impressed enough
They have transferred him
No money for research, they say
And since when does a Priority One
project become short of money?
Day 98
The working climate is strained
McRich just quit
without another word
And Anderson?
Disappeared without a trace
No one knows anything
Well, I could imagine
they have fired him
after the trouble he made
but why does nobody know anything?
Seems as though I am the only
one left working on Pandora
Day 103
Today I received an anonymous letter
containing only a
micro SD card
The data encrypted
I think, they are...
from the... laboratory
Someone passed Pandora's
documents to me
McRich perhaps? What if they
want to silence him?
Maybe I'm getting paranoid but
isn't it a strange coincidence
that Anderson had this...
accident at this precise moment?
I need to watch out whom I trust
Day 116
Section seven has been closed
Lacking money, they say
Project Pandora?
Project Pandora discontinued
for ever
all recordings deleted
but why deleting all documents
when discontinuing a project?
I've been transferred
Priority Four
Well and today's question is:
What goes wrong when a virologist
suddenly has to research on hay fever?
Let's find it out
Day 120
My inquiries to the management
attract attention
Just now in the corridor
Wilhemsen himself asked me
to stop nosing around
He said he could not guarantee
my safety any more
Whatever that may mean?
Let's find it out
Day 123
My last
Asking questions became
quite unpleasant
I'm being... watched...
My telephone's tapped
My apartment...
Someone broke into my apartment
I've put the SD card to
a save place and ehm...
Maybe I'm becoming paranoid but
I've got the feeling, that this is...
the only reason why I...
why nothing has happened to me yet
Well who knows...
That is all